here is a patriot of his country by
вот патриот своей страны
patriots Patriot of the Soviet repair of the
патриотами Патриот ремонта
Soviet repair, are you a Soviet one,
советского ну вас собой Советский еще
or is it a new
или это новые
Soviet day of the Soviet repair Well, you
советского дня советского ремонта Ну
see, I am a Soviet person
видно я Советский человек
A patriot of the Soviet repair,
Патриот советского ремонта
and you, by the way, the year of birth I am 81
а вы кстати года рождения Я 81
now I can’t find young people in the Soviet
сейчас молодежь найти она Советском
Union at all or
Союзе вообще не вспоминает либо
remember what is there  the dictatorship was they didn’t
вспоминает что там диктатура была они не
live they don’t understand how it was a
жили они не понимают насколько это было
free country mentally we all
свободная страна душевно у нас все было
agreed
согласны
my hometown
мой родной город
in Odessa
в Одессе
Yes, as I said a
Да я как говорил
foreigner I talk to Yaroslavl
иностранец Я говорю с Ярославле
and everyone
и все
went for a walk, pours,
пошли говорит погуляем наливает запивая
drinks, they wanted to Odessa, they wanted to pickle,
выпивает хотели Одесса хотели травануть
so
поэтому
it’s now starting to find fault  And when
это сейчас начинает придираться А когда
I was without problems
я был без проблем
But
А вот
I studied at the school with me Odessa was a
я в училище учился со мной Одессит был
native for how many 17 years I lived in Odessa I
коренной сколько 17 лет жил в Одессе
came to study Orlovsky to act
приехал учились Орловского поступать
together we did 4 years we lived with him
вместе поступили 4 года мы с ним
no problems
жили никаких проблем
look here I just try to chat
смотрите вот я просто я стараюсь чат
roulettes of our Ukrainian youth, also
рулетки молодежи наши украинской тоже
Russian  it’s right to talk about the
российской правильно рассказывать о
Soviet Union, so, well, it was a
Советском Союзе так вот ну что это было
good country, everything, but they’re like jute from me
хорошая страна все но они с меня типа
and they say that there
джут и говорят что типа ну там продуктов
were no products, like you’re an older person,
не было как вот вы более старший человек
more experienced, how would you advise me to
более опытный как бы вы мне посоветовали
argue young people about the Soviet
аргументировать молодежи про Советский
Union Yes,
Союз Да никак
not at all  I can even convince you that the children are 40 years old
не могу убедить даже вот дети это 40 лет
they
они
know a lot they saw 80 years of birth
многое знает видели 80 года рождения
the eighth year of birth is
восьмого года рождения
no longer considered the Soviet Union
уже не считается Советский Союза
Soviet solo It was a long time ago we still don’t
Советской соло Это было давно мы еще не
know what I’m 81 look I meet
знаем я что же 81 смотрите Я встречаю
my classmates here we had a
своих одноклассников вот у нас была
meeting of classmates so I brought  the flag of the
встреча одноклассников так я принес флаг
Soviet Union the groom we went to the first
Советского Союза грум мы пошли первый
grade of the Soviet school I almost got
класс советскую школу Мне чуть морду не
stuffed in the face, you know They began to hate so much
набили понимаете Они настолько стали
Well, what did the Soviet Union do
ненавидеть Ну что тебе Советский Союз
bad to you, you had toys yes, the
сделал плохое у тебя игрушки были да
school uniform was Well, yes, it was [ __ ] It
школьная форма была Ну да уёбищная Такая
was brown, it was more gerasi Well,
была коричневая такая какой более гераси
it was, look at you  They don’t start with this,
Ну была вот смотри ты Не с этого не
I’ll be here
начинаешь они на ты я буду вот
In the ninety-first year, when Ukraine
В девяносто первом году когда Украина
became an independent Ukraine, the state
стала независимая Украина государство
it occupied Well, Russia I just
оно оно занимало Ну Россия Я просто
occupied one of the first places in Europe in terms of
занимала одно из первых мест в Европе по
economy,
экономике
in many it outlived even Germany I do
во многих он переживал даже Германию Я
n’t even say more anymore
уже не говорю больше больше даже близко
did not stand close to Ukraine,
не стояла с Украины
this is the most
это самая
developed economy was the country of
экономика развита была страна
education It was the best
образование Было самое лучшее
industry the best ships
промышленность самая лучшая корабли
ships produced 40 percent of the world's
корабли выпускали 40 процентов мировых
ships were produced in Ukraine
кораблей выпускалась на Украине Я своим
were better in Europe yes
тоже вот игру Мы были лучше в Европе да
When In the ninety-first year They
Когда В девяносто первом году Они
say nonsense we didn’t have
говорят а чушь у нас тогда не было
food back then a little jeans were brought from
продуктов чуть джинсы привозили из
Europe we didn’t have a damn queue
Европы у нас ни хрена не было в очереди
were for bread
были за хлебом
[laughter]
[смех]
I love this fairy tale so much that when Ukraine
Я так люблю эту сказку что когда Украина
became independent it  there, a little bit in Europe, it’s a
стала независима она там чуть в Европе
pity that grandfather merged, I run to drink splendor by us
жалко дед слился бегу пить пышность нами
a kilogram right at a time, autumn, and buttocks are
килограмм прям за раз осень а попок
more and more important YouTube driving
ц дуже и дуже важнева YouTube загоняя
us through the cardiorka into the shadow ban and the
нас через кардиорке в теневые бан и
side of the face is not shown to people in
дужебока вида не показывается людям в
private, information about streams is shown
частном на показывается информация про
because in order to be a little
стримы потому для того чтобы мало
operational  stars rush forest right at
оперативный звездок пик пущица прям за
a time and try there in a kilogram about cream
раз а попыт там в килограмме о Крим
video
видео
information and we
информация и мы с вами
will show you
покажем вам
[music]
[музыка]